module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Support for a vineyard. It basically amounted to a bunch of carrying heavy things in the hot sun.', 
    a: 'RA',
    b: 'JoshP',
    c: 'Shannon',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Professional legal drug dealer', 
    a: 'Marion',
    b: 'JoCo',
    c: 'Kell',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'I was once a telemarketing fundraiser with a boss who behaved exactly like Michael Scott.', 
    a: 'Kendra',
    b: 'Mitch',
    c: 'Aaron',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Regional Manager for dishwashing supply company. I got caustic chemical burns on my body, had 300 cockroaches fall out of a machine I was servicing with an employee and spill all over me, and got a concussion when I slammed my head into a shelf working on a ridealong.', 
    a: 'Mercan',
    b: 'Brady',
    c: 'RA',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Layout Editor at Gatehouse Media', 
    a: 'Taylor',
    b: 'Brendan',
    c: 'Brandi',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Manager at Gamestop', 
    a: 'Tyler N',
    b: 'Aaron',
    c: 'Billy',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Cashier at a local pizza joint', 
    a: 'Carolyn',
    b: 'Sean',
    c: 'Elizabeth',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Executive Assistant to a CEO who made me schedule driving lessons for his wife who just bought a Range Rover and didn\'t know how to drive it', 
    a: 'Marion',
    b: 'Smashley',
    c: 'Haley',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Bus Boy at fried chicken restaurant', 
    a: 'Brandon',
    b: 'Brendon',
    c: 'JoCo',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Trivia contestant', 
    a: 'West',
    b: 'ChelsB',
    c: 'ChelsB',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
